(Penny:)Okay, it's done.
(Penny:)Look, guys, for the future,
I don't mind killing the big spiders...
(Penny:)...but you have to at least try
with the little ones.
(Sheldon:)Penny, please. We're facing a far more
serious problem than stray arachnids.
- Sheldon, it's not that bad.
- Not bad? It's horrible.
(Sheldon:)You hear stories about this sort of thing.
You never think it will happen to you.
(Leonard:)So they steamed your dumplings.
Get over it.
(Leonard:)New topic, please.
(Howard:)All right, Penny.
Let me take this opportunity to point out...
(Howard:)...that you are looking particularly
ravishing today.
(Penny:)Not with a thousand condoms, Howard.
(Howard:)So there is a number.
(Penny:)Okay. New topic, please.
(Penny:)Hey, did you hear the people
in 5-A are moving out?
- No. Shh-shh-shh!
- Why?
- The people upstairs are moving out.
- No.
(Sheldon:)The horror.
(Leonard:)Why would you just say something
like that?